迪恩  你弟弟正步入危险
Your brother is heading down a dangerous road, dean.
好吧
Okay.
我入伙了
I'm in.
你告诉迪恩我们的行动了吗
You gonna tell dean about what we're doing?
我正想着要怎么说合适呢
I just got to figure out the right way to say it.
他会发现的
He's gonna find out,
如果不是从你口中得知  他会发火的
And if it's not from you, he's gonna be pissed.
反正他都会发火的
He's gonna pissed anyway.
你满意了吧
You satisfied?
你为什么那么相信她
Why do you trust her so much?
迪恩  是她帮我逃离莉莉丝的魔爪
I told you, dean, she helped me go after lilith.
谢谢  诠释得很生动
Well, thanks for the thumbnail -- real vivid.
我在楼下的时候  一定发生了什么大事
Something major must've happened while I was downstairs,
因为我回来的时候  你正和恶魔亲热
'cause I come back and -- and you're bff with a demon?
要不要说下细节呢
You want to fill in a little detail?
当然啦  迪恩  我们都说下自己的事吧
Sure, dean. let's trade stories.
你先吧  地狱怎样  别太啰嗦
You first. how was hell? don't spare the details.
怎么啦
What?
特德喜欢使唤人  是吧
Ted's kind of cracking the whip, isn't he?
你以为我喜欢晚回家吗
You think I like coming home late?
我都快累死了
I'm working my ass off.
好吧
Okay.
对不起
Sorry.
不  是我对不住你
No, I'm sorry.
对不起
I'm sorry.
漫长的一天
Long day.
我今天遇到了吉尔·马丁
Oh, hey. I ran into jill martin today.
盖瑞星期六过40岁生日
Gary's turning 40 on saturday.
是吗
Yeah?
她请我们参加生日派对
She invited us to the party.
你怎么跟她说的
What'd you tell her?
我答应她去啊
That we'd go.
你开玩笑吧
You're kidding.
怎么啦
What?
你喜欢盖瑞的
You like gary.
不错  但这并不表示
Yeah, that doesn't mean
我想和那个家伙浪费我的周末时光
That I want to waste my saturday night with him.
我以为你会去的
I thought you'd want to go.
我真不敢相信
I don't believe you.
没事的
I-it's fine.
我会  我会打给吉尔  告诉她我们不去了
I'll -- I'll call jill and tell her we can't make it.
今晚你是怎么啦
What's with you tonight?
感觉你想找人吵架
It's like you want to have a fight or something.
[邪恶力量 第4季第14集]
没错  我正想告诉你呢
Yeah, that's what I'm telling you.
没有风暴  庄稼收成也好  一切正常
No storms, no -- no bad crops, nothing.
是的
Yeah.
好的  我会继续留意的
Yeah, I will keep looking.
你也留意下  行吗
You keep looking, too, okay?
好的 再联系吧
All right, talk soon.
嘿
Hey.
起床开工啦  老兄
Up and at 'em, kiddo.
你起得真早  在干嘛呢
You're up early. what are you doing?
没什么  刚上洗手间
Nothing. I was in the can.
是吗
Yeah?
对啊  要我给你画张画吗
Yeah. want me to draw you a picture?
不  还是算了吧
No, I'll pass.
我找到新活了  爱荷华州  贝德福德
I found a job -- bedford, iowa.
有个男人用嫩肉针砸死了她的妻子
Guy beat his wife's brains out with a meat tenderizer.
天哪
Yikes.
这个是两个月内第三起
And get this -- third local inside two months
杀害妻子的事故了
To gank his wife.
都没有前兆  婚姻也一直美满
No priors on any of them, all happily married.
看来像是“奥齐与哈丽雅特”(美国经典爱情故事)
Sounds like "Ozzie and Harriet."
更像是“闪灵”(美国恐怖片)
More like "the Shining."
好吧  我们还是探个究竟
All right, well, I guess we better have a look.
警察局怎么还派人来
Why does the p.d. keep sending you guys?
我说了不需要律师
I already said I don't want a lawyer.
他们正准备对你行刑呢
They're lining up the firing squad.
我承认自己有罪
I'm pleading guilty.
好吧  既然你不需要我们当你的代理律师
All right, look, you don't want us to represent you --
那也行
That's fine.
其实  对于你我来说也不算坏事
In fact, it's probably not a bad idea, between you and me.
我们只想搞清楚是怎么回事
We just want to understand what happened.
就这么简单
That's all.
本森先生
Mr. benson...
拜托
...please.
事情就是
What happened was...
我杀了我妻子
I killed my wife.
至于原因嘛
And you want to know why?
她没征求我意见就擅自做了决定
Because she made plans without asking me.
那当时  你是什么感觉
When it happened, how did you feel?
意识模糊  失控了吗
Disoriented? out of control?
是不是像被支配了一样
Like something possessed you to do it?
我知道自己做了什么
I knew exactly what I was doing.
我很清醒
I was crystal clear.
那你为什么要那样做
Then why did you do it?
我不知道
I don't know.
我爱她
I loved her.
我们在一起很开心
We were happy.
9千美元
9 g's.
这笔帐可不小
That's a hefty bill.
你从哪得到的
Where did you get that?
这无关紧要  我们有就是了
Doesn't matter. we have it.
看看  这些付款
See, certain charges --
都是你不想让你太太知道的
Ones you don't want the missus to know --
均签匿名例如“尙奇娱乐”
They show up under shady names like "m & c entertainment."
没错  不过我不知道你在说什么
Yeah, I don't know what you're talking about.
打个比方  就像你在色情酒吧丢了信用卡
Oh, you're dropping plastic at a nudie bar, for instance.
我们只想弄清楚真相  本森先生
We just... want to know the truth, mr. benson.
她叫贾丝敏
Her name was...jasmine.
她是个脱衣舞女吗
She was a stripper?
老弟  人家真名叫贾丝敏
Dude, her name was jasmine.
我也不希望走到这一步
I didn't mean for it to happen.
我不喜欢去脱衣舞酒吧
I don't like to go to strip bars.
我的好朋友开了一个单身派对
My buddy was having a bachelor party,
然后  就遇到了她
And...there she was.
贾丝敏
Jasmine.
她走到我面前
She came right up to me.
然后
And...
我  我不知道  她很
I-i don't know, s-she was just...
完美
Perfect.
是我喜欢的类型
Everything that I wanted.
只要你付的钱够多  谁都可能成为你梦中情人
Well, you pay enough, anybody will be anything.
这和钱无关
It wasn't about the money.
甚至不关乎性
It wasn't even about the sex.
就是
It was --
我不知道
I don't know.
我不知道是什么
I don't know what it was.
这个很难解释
It's hard to explain.
你妻子发现了
And your wife found out?
没有  她一无所知
No, she never had a clue.
那你为什么要杀了她
Then why'd you kill her?
为了贾丝敏
For jasmine.
她说我们能永远在一起
She said we would be together forever,
如果 如果
If -- if only j--
薇姬
Vicki was...
死了
Muerte.
然后  我和贾丝敏约好见面
Afterwards, me and jasmine were supposed to meet,
可是她一直没出现
And she never showed.
我不知道她姓啥住哪
I don't know where she lives. I don't know her last name.
我甚至连她的真名都不知道
I don't even know her real first name.
我是个大笨蛋
I'm an idiot.
你不想跟警察交代这些事情吗
And you didn't think to tell this to the cops?
有什么用
What for?
那个脱衣舞女没有杀人
The stripper didn't do it.
人是我杀的
I did it.
我罪有应得
And I know what I deserve.
法官没判我死刑
Judge doesn't give me the death sentence,
我就自行了断
I'll just do it myself.
昨晚很糟吗
Rough night?
昨晚很开心啊
Fun night.
早上不爽
Rough morning.
我能帮上什么忙吗
Can I help you?
是的
Uh, yes.
FBI特工  斯泰尔斯
I'm special agent stiles -- fbi.
你就是卡拉·罗伯茨教授吗
You're dr. cara roberts?
没错  是我
Far as I know.
你为州长做事吗
You do some work with the sheriff's department?
是啊  我不在急诊室干苦力的时候就去
Yeah, when I'm not slogging it through the e.r.
这是个小镇  我们都有多重的活
It's a small town. we multitask.
我有一个案子  想问你一些问题
Well, I have some questions about a case --
实际上  有几个案子
About several cases, actually.
介意我坐下吗  太好了
You mind if I sit? great.
亚当·本森  吉姆·威利  还有斯蒂夫·斯耐德
Uh, Adam Benson, Jim Wylie, and Steve Snyder?
噢  那几个杀了自己妻子的男人
Oh, yeah. the men who killed their wives.
你负责病例检查  是吗
You handled the work-ups, right?
对妻子进行了尸检  对凶手则进行毒理检验
Mm-hmm. autopsies for the wives and tox screens for the perps.
特别针对此案进行的检查
Two-for-one special.
有发现吗
You find anything?
没有
Not really.
女尸的需氧量很清晰
I mean, c.o.d. on the women was pretty clear --
整个生理系统也很正常
There was nothing unusual in their system.
那几个丈夫呢
What about the husbands?
我能再看看你的徽章吗
Can I see your badge again?
有一点
There was one thing --
血检时发现了点异样
Um, an anomaly in the blood work.
最让我觉得奇怪的是
And I remember thinking how strange it was
三个男人的血检都有
That it showed up in all three of the men.
是什么
That what showed up?
催产素
Oxytocin.
而且其含量高到足以让人发疯
And their levels were crazy high.
催产素是什么
Uh, oxytocin?
是一种激素
Mm-hmm, it's a hormone
在分娩期  哺乳期以及性交中产生
That's produced during childbirth, lactation, and sex.
明白
Okay.
俗称爱情激素
People call it the love hormone.
还记得你第一次坠入爱河时的感觉吗
Um, you know how it feels when you first fall in love --
双腿发软  心中有抹倩影挥之不去
The whole weak-in-the-knees, tattoo-you-on-my-chest thing?
那就是催产素在作怪
That's oxytocin.
当然  它终究会消逝
Of course, it eventually fades,
而你则陷入了感情的轮回里无法自拔
And then you're stuck with every relationship ever,
这种感觉就像消除纹身一样痛苦
That and the painful regimen of tattoo removal.
我错过了什么
What'd I miss?
这是我的搭档  梅铎克探员
This is my partner -- Agent Murdock.
拜托  探员叫起来太不亲切啦
Please, "agent" sounds so formal.
你可以叫我迪恩
You can call me dean.
我是罗伯茨医生
I'm Dr. Roberts.
那么
So, um...
还有啥我能帮忙的
Can I help you with anything else?
对了  还有一件事
Uh...sure. just one more thing.
这个化学的  这个
This chemical, this...
-催产素  -催产素
- Oxytocin. ...- oxytocin
你查出了含量过高的原因了吗
What would cause those high levels that you found?
前所未闻
Nothing that I've ever seen.
好吧  就这样吧
Okay. that's it.
十分感谢  医生
Thanks, Doc.
多句嘴  试下多脂的早餐
By the way, uh, try a greasy breakfast.
对宿醉很好
Best thing for a hangover.
悠着点  伙计  我可是这儿唯一的医学博士
Watch it, buddy. I'm the only m.d. here.
老弟  你真是让我刮目相看啊
Dude, you totally c-blocked me.
威利和斯耐德都认罪了  对吗
So, Wylie and Snyder fessed up, huh?
一个提空了自己的退休金
One emptied his i.r.a.,
而另一个  提空了他孩子的大学基金
The other, his kid's college fund --
所有事都指向同一点
All on the same thing.
包养脱衣舞女吗
Live nude girls?
俱乐部的名字叫甜蜜旅车
Club called the honey wagon.
这两人也和叫贾丝敏的脱衣舞女搞过吗
These guys have affairs, too, with a stripper also known as Jasmine?
是  又不全是
Yes and no.
有趣的正是这里
This is where it gets interesting.
每个人钓上的女人都不同
Each guy hooked up with a different chick.
那么  这些女孩又是怎么搅在一起的
So, what, these girls all connected somehow?
他们所描述的脱衣舞女郎都有一个共同之处
Well, they all described their stripper in the same way,
而且完完全全的一致
The exact same way --
完美  他们的理想型
Perfect and everything that they wanted.
是吗  至少他们幻想的是
Yeah, at least they'll dream
-芭比女郎让他们去谋杀自己的妻子  -就是这样
- Barbie convinced them to murder their wives. - there's that.
他们就像是中了某种爱情魔咒
You know, it's almost like they were under some kind of love spell.
绝对没错
Sure seems that way.
那魔咒让他们彻底疯狂
Which caused them to become totally psychotic.
完全正确
Absolutely.
你看起来很兴奋
You seem pretty cheery.
脱衣舞女啊  萨姆  尤物啊
Strippers, sammy. strippers.
我们可是在调查一单有脱衣舞女的案子噢
We are on an actual case involving strippers.
真是一劳永逸
Finally.
我找这三个女孩
I'm looking for three girls --
贾丝敏  奥罗拉和艾莉尔
Jasmine, Aurora, and Ariel.
你真觉得这些名字对我有意义
You seriously think those names mean anything to me?
有个染红发大约5尺9  另一个是亚洲人
One's a redhead about 5'9". the other one's asian about --
你知道我要和多少女孩打交道吗
Do you have any idea how many girls I deal with?
假名  假发  都是假的
Fake names, fake hair, fake...
你应该有一些文件存根之类的
You got to have some sort of paperwork, check stubs,
记录她们的行踪
Some way to keep track of the strippers.
别搞笑了  都是外国妹
Please. exotic dancers --
我只管给她们钱
Independent contractors working for cash.
其他的我都不管
I stay out of their hair.
她们给我留下点钱就行
They stay out of what little I have left.
你的三个客人杀了自己的妻子
Three of your customers murdered their wives.
你不觉得那很诡异吗
You don't think that that's weird?
是啊  我觉得超诡异
Yeah, I think that's super-freakin' weird.
可这些都不关我事
But you know what it ain't? my problem.
有发现吗
Any luck?
没  你呢
No. you?
有一点  我刚和鲍比谈了谈
A little. I just talked to bobby.
行内有个说法
We officially have a theory.
-是什么  -海妖
- What's that? - siren.
希腊传说中的海妖吗
Like greek-myth siren?
“奥德赛”中描写那个
Like "the odyssey"?
我读过
Hey, I read.
是啊  事实上  海妖不是什么神话
Yeah, actually, but the siren's not actually a myth.
更像是某种专门猎捕男人的尤物
It's more of a beautiful creature that prey on men,
用海妖之歌引诱他们
Entice them with their siren song.
我猜是  “欢迎来到丛林”(枪炮玫瑰乐队)
Let me guess -- "welcome to the jungle"?
不不  应该是涡轮乐队的“樱桃派”
No, no. warrant's "cherry pie"?
歌声充满隐喻
Their song is more of a metaphor --
隐含着它们的召唤和引诱
Like their call, their allure.
小嘴一挥就能把男人搞得和僵尸一样乖吗
So they shake their thing and the guys zombie out?
可以这么说  海妖生活在海岛上
Basically, yeah. sirens live on islands.
海员会疯狂地追逐她们
Sailors would chase them,
冲向礁石密布的海域
Completely ignoring the rocky shores,
结果把自己撞得粉碎
And dash themselves to pieces.
就像亚当他们三人
Sounds like adam and his buddies.
如果你是09年的海妖
If you were a siren in '09
正想要玩弄一些笨蛋
And looking to ruin a bunch of morons,
你打算从哪里下手
Where would you set up shop?
那些勾引男人的尤物
So, whatever floats the guy's boat,
都长成那样吗
That's what they look like?
是啊  海妖能读取人的思想
Yeah. you see, sirens can read minds.
她们知道你最想要什么
They see what you want most,
她们能伪装自己
And then they can kind of, like, cloak themselves --
就像某种幻术
You know, like an illusion.
也就是说可能只有一只海妖
So it could all be the same chick,
变成不同的梦中女孩
Morphing into different dream girls?
恩  很有可能
Yeah, actually. probably.
海妖一般都喜欢独居
Sirens are usually pretty solitary.
我们怎么杀它
How do we kill it?
鲍比正在查
Bobby's working on it.
就算我们知道怎么杀
But even if we figure that out...
我们怎么找到它  它可能是任何人
How the hell are we gonna find it? it could be anybody.
你好  美女
Hi, belle.
以为你不来了呢
Thought you'd never come.
没事了  她睡着了
It's okay. she's asleep.
莱尼  你真棒
Lenny, you're amazing...
这么照顾她
Taking care of her like this.
大部分人都会把她送敬老院
Most guys would have put her in a nursing home.
这没什么
It's no big deal.
她是我妈妈
She's my mom.
如我所说  好棒啊
Like I said -- amazing.
宝贝
Baby...
我爱死你了
...i love you so much.
你那么照顾我和你妈妈
The way you take care of me and your mom --
你多么的可人
You're so sweet...
又很强壮
And strong.
我只希望你能轻松一点
I just wish you didn't have to carry it all.
你妈妈占用了你所有的时间
I mean, your mom takes up all your time.
只要她在  我们就没法快乐
As long as she's around, we can't really be happy.
她也没那么糟
She's not so bad.
我可以和你在一起
I could be with you...
永远
Forever...
要是你妈妈不在这里
If only your mom wasn't here.
难道你不想和我永生相伴吗
Don't you want to be with me forever?
想啊
Yeah.
你知道我想的
Yeah, you know I do.
那就杀了你妈妈吧
Then bash your mother's brains in.
宝贝儿  就算是为了我
Baby, do it for me.
去吧  宝贝
Do it, baby.
好的  行啊
Yeah, okay.
只要你说
If you say so.
我爱你
I love you.
嗨  萨姆
Hey, sam.
萨姆  你在吗
Sam? you there?
莱尼·布里斯托尔是另一位海妖的受害者
Lenny bristol was definitely another siren vic.
-你去看他了吗  -是的
- You got in to see him?  -Yep.
他带了一个名叫贝尔的脱衣舞女回家
Said he brought a stripper home named belle.
几个小时后  他杀死了自己的母亲
Couple hours later, he offed his mother.
贝尔也从现场消失了
Belle, of course, went m.i.a.
等等  他杀了自己的妈妈吗
Wait. he killed his mom?
那个女人指使的
Woman he was closest to.
对了  你忘带手机了
Yeah, you, uh... forgot your cellphone.
嗨  鲍比
Hey, bobby.
萨姆  找到她了吗
Sam, did you find her yet?
还没
Uh, no,
不过她好像仍在作案
And doesn't seem like she's slowing down any.
你那边怎么样  有什么新发现吗
What about you? got anything?
从尘土弥漫的希腊诗歌中找到了一些传说
Well, some lore from a dusty greek poem.
狭隘且有点模糊
Shockingly, it's a little vague.
稍等  我开一下免提
Oh, hold on a sec. I'm gonna put you on speaker.
上面说  你需要一把青铜匕首
It says you need "a bronze dagger
上面要沾着在咒语之歌控制下的水手之血
Covered in the blood of a sailor under the spell of the song."
这是什么意思
What the hell does that mean?
问到点子上了
You got me.
我们正着手于一项三千年的电话游戏
We're dealing with 3,000 years of the telephone game here.
最佳猜测
Best guess?
海妖的咒语与曲无关
Well, the siren's spell ain't got nothing to do with any song.
更像是某种毒素或毒液
It's most likely some kind of toxin or venom.
从受害者血液中获得
Something she gets in the vics' blood.
因此他们寻找傀儡
That makes them go all manchurian candidate.
你觉得呢  她利用性来传染男人吗
Uh, what do you think? she infects the men during sex?
有可能
Maybe.
斯幽皮儿那撤性病
Supernatural std.
不论发生什么
Well, however it happens,
一旦成功了  海妖就会跟进
Once it's done, the siren's got to watch her back.
如果她吞食毒液
If she gets a dose of her own medicine...
则自取灭亡
It kills her.
就像是毒蛇用毒液把自己毒死了
Like a snake getting iced by its own venom.
那我们只需在监狱里找个提取下
So we just got to find a way to juice one of the o.j.s in jail?
没那么简单
It's not that easy.
那些人现在已经不受咒语的控制了
None of those guys are under the spell anymore.
就没什么办法能让你拿到血液了吗
Haven't got a clue where you're gonna get the blood you need.
我有个主意
I think I might have an idea.
一定要小心
Be careful.
这些妖精非常狡猾
These things are tricky bastards.
在你不知情的时候  他们就可能把你包围
Wrap you up in knots before you know what hit you.
罗伯茨博士
Dr. Roberts.
斯泰尔斯探员
Agent Stiles.
等不及了是吗
Can't stay away, huh?
实际上  我们是来谈正事的
Actually, we're here on business
关于那个血样  那个高浓度的
About the blood samples, the ones with the high...
催产素
...you know, oxytocin.
你还保存着吗
Do you still have them?
很好  正好我们要用
Good. we need them.
用来做什么
What for?
不好意思  罗伯茨博士
Excuse me, dr. roberts?
什么事
Yeah?
抱歉
Excuse me.
我们这里有点事情要处理  哥们
Uh, we're a little busy here, buddy.
我也一样  兄弟
Yeah, so am i, pal.
博士  让我们单独聊会好吗
Doc, could you give us a sec, please?
-当然  -谢谢
- Sure.  - thanks.
您贵姓
What's your name?
尼克·门罗  你俩呢
Nick Monroe. what's yours?
我是萨姆·斯泰尔斯特工
I'm special agent sam stiles.
这是我的搭档迪恩·梅铎克
This is my partner -- dean murdock.
你是哪个部门的
What office you from?
奥马哈市  暴力专案组
Omaha -- violent-crimes unit.
战略空军司令部派我过来
My s.a.c. sent me down here
调查一下这些杀人凶手
To see about the murders.
你们呢
You?
国防委员会
D.c.
副部长派我们来的
Our assistant director assigned us.
哪位副部长
Which a.d.?
麦克·凯撒
Mike Kaiser.
你们的警号是多少
What are your badge numbers?
你逗我玩呢
You're kidding, right?
这只是我们见面的形式而已
I'm just following protocol.
别那么麻烦了  给我们副部长打个电话吧
Look, man, whatever. just call our a.d.
他会跟你说清楚的
He'll sort things out, huh?
请帮我转接副部长凯撒
Uh, yeah, assistant director kaiser, please.
部长你好  我是特工尼克·门罗
Yeah, sir, hello. it's agent nick monroe.
我想跟你了解一下你部门的两个人
I'm calling about... two of your men --
斯泰尔斯和梅铎克
Stiles and murdock?
他们可能搞错了  正在插手我的案件
Uh, it seems that they've been put on my case by mistake.
你是在质疑我们当局吗
Are you questioning my authority?
不是  不是  阁下  我没有在质疑
No, no, no, sir. I'm not questioning.
你可以愚弄我
You could have fooled me.
但我已经查了  孩子  国防委员会有管辖权
Last time I checked, son, d.c. has jurisdiction.
还是我弄错了吗
Or am I wrong?
没有  部长
No, sir
很好
Well, good.
如果下次你还想浪费我的时间
Well, the next time you want to waste my time
来问这些无聊的问题  我劝你还是省省吧
With stupid questions, don't.
这些糊涂蛋
Those idjits.
对不起  哥们
Well, I'm sorry, guys.
别再搞这样的事就好了
Just don't let it happen again.
这案子你们跟到哪了
So, where are you at with this?
你呢
Where are you at with this?
我正要对这些血样进行调查
Well, I was about to run the perps' blood work.
我已经查了  无果而终
I already checked. it's a dead end.
-是吗  -是的
- Oh, yeah?  - yeah.
我觉得能找到一些东西
Well, get this -- I feel like I found something
把这些杀人犯们都联系起来
That connects all the murderers.
真的吗
Really?
他们都是脱衣舞女
They were all banging strippers
来自同一个俱乐部
From the same club.
说的不错
You don't say.
我们一起去那看看怎么样
What do you say we go down there and check it out?
这就是问题所在  尼克
Well, here's the thing, nick.
我们喜欢独来独往
See, we're kind of lone wolves --
知道吗
You know what?
这想法听起来不错
That sounds like an excellent idea.
请稍候我们一会
Just give me a second with my partner.
很快的
And we'll, uh -- one second.
过来一下
Come here.
兄弟  你得跟着他
Dude, you got to stay with him.
-什么  -别让他挡我们的路
- What?  - keep him out of the way.
为什么是我
Why me?
因为我得去拿血样
'Cause I got to get the blood samples.
那我跟他在一起做什么呢
What the hell am I supposed to do with him?
带他去那个脱衣舞女俱乐部
Just take him to the strip club,
关注一下海妖的事
Keep an eye out for the siren.
好嘛  迪恩  只须把精力放在那些裸女上
Come on, dean, just -- just focus on the naked girls.
你就会忘了他的存在
You'll forget he's even there.
我不是为你这么做的  我是为了那些女孩们
I'm not doing this for you. I'm doing it for the girls.
坐我的车吧  最好别抱怨
We're taking my ride. No complaining about the tunes.
不是吧  你是开这辆英帕拉吗
No way. you drive an impala?
对
Yeah.
是67年的对吗  是个327四腔式的
It's a '67, right? it's a 327 4-barrel.
说的不错
Yeah, actually.
太漂亮了
It's a thing of beauty.
谢谢
Thanks.
你是怎么跟局里谈的
How the hell did you talk the bureau
他们会让你开自己的车
Into letting you drive your own wheels?
你要这个血样是因为
And you want this blood because...
我们想做一些测试
We'd like to run some tests.
所有的测试我都会亲自做
You know, I've run every test there is.
这是我的工作呀
It's, um...my job.
注意我的工作服
Notice the lab coat.
我们了解到有一位专家  想证明一个理论
We know a specialist who would like to try out a theory.
既然你这么说了
If you say so.
怎么回事
What the hell?
怎么了
What?
血样没了
The blood's gone.
都是我的错
"Nobody's fault but mine."
75年的策帕林飞艇
Oh, oh, oh, zeppelin recorded it, '75.
这是一首盲人韦利·约翰森的曲子
It was a cover of a blind willie johnson tune.
真棒
Nice.
“你吓到我了”
"you shook me."
69年  首张专辑  威利·狄克逊写得
Oh, '69, debut album, written by willie dixon.
还有呢
And?
还有什么
And what?
是威利·狄克逊和巴顿·雷诺合作完成的
Written by willie dixon and j.b. lenoir.
伙计
Dude.
Dude!
作为一个联邦调查局探员  你还不算是混蛋
You know, for a fed, you're not a total dick.
我们不都是联邦调查局探员吗
Aren't we both feds?
是  不  我只是  你知道
Yeah. no, I just, you know --
不是所有探员都跟我们一样酷  不是吗
Not a lot of feds as cool as us, huh?
那么  伙计  那案子到底是怎么回事
So, what the hell with this case, man?
怎么可能一个女孩子说服4个不同的人去杀人
How does a girl talk four different johns into murder?
疯狂的世界
Crazy world.
我猜
I guess.
我跟你坦白说吧
Hey, can I level with you? hmm.
我发现点奇怪的事
I found something kind of weird.
你把你的疑虑带到正确的地方上了
You brought your weird to the right spot.
跟我说说看呢
Lay it on me.
我今早去了犯罪现场
I went to the crime scene this morning.
看见他们把这个装了起来
Saw them bagging this up.
所以我检查了所有档案
So I went back through all the files.
发现每个犯罪现场
It turns out a flower just like that
都有这样的花
Was found at every crime scene.
像是故意留下的吗
Like it was left on purpose?
有时候一个连环杀人案凶手
I mean, you know, sometimes a serial killer
总会在现场留下个东西  比如说电话卡
Will leave an object behind, like a calling card.
但是这个案子
But with this case?
跟你说实话吧
To tell you the truth...
我完全理不清头绪
I got no idea what's going on.
我想我知道了
I think I might.
我以前见过这样的花
I've seen a flower like this before.
我们已经看了两遍了
we've watched them twice.
不管取走血样的是谁
Whoever took the blood...
肯定对这些录影带动过手脚
Must have tampered with the tapes.
谁能自由出入你的办公室
who has access to your office?
每个人  我不锁门的
Everyone. I don't lock it.
你怎么
You what?
我从没碰上过这种问题
I've never had this problem before.
那些血究竟有多重要
What is so important about the blood, anyway?
有人对犯人下了药
I think someone drugged the men
让他们犯罪
made them commit murder.
什么
What?
怎样的药
What kind of drug?
我还不清楚
Uh, I'm not sure yet.
我不知道
I don't know.
我审问过这些人
I mean, I interviewed those guys,
他们有自己的理由
And they had their reasons.
是  但是他们都深爱着受害人
Yeah, but they all loved their victims.
我相信他们
I'm sure they did.
拜托
come on.
难道你没谈过恋爱吗
Haven't you ever been in a relationship
当你深爱某人时
Where you really loved somebody
仍想将他们杀死
And still kind of wanted to bash their head in?
听起来你感同身受
Sounds like you're speaking from experience.
对不起  我无意问及你的私生活
Look, I'm sorry. i-i don't mean to pry.
没事
It's okay.
是我提起来的
I was the one who brought it up.
是吗
Really?
这是药
It's medicine.
我是医生
I'm a doctor.
他叫卡尔
His name was carl.
我们结了婚
And we were married.
发生了什么
So what happened?
只是生活
Life happened.
我不知道  我爱过他
I don't know. I mean, I loved him.
现在还爱
I still do, I guess.
但是  我不知道
But, um, I don't know.
就像是某一天我认真审视了一下
It's just like one day I looked up,
好像自己跟一个陌生人生活在一起
And I was living with a stranger.
然后
And...
你知道意思吧
You know what I mean, right?
我想是吧
I guess.
或者  也许我不知道
Or...i don't know. maybe.
人总会变
People change.
上帝啊  我知道自己变了
God, I know I did.
但是没有丝毫的罪恶感
But it's nothing to feel guilty about.
事情就这么发生了
It happens.
所以你们俩分开了吗
So you two split up?
是  可以这么形容
Yeah, I suppose that's a word for it.
你要接吗
You need to get that?
不
No.
现在不接
Not right now.
不管怎样
Whatever.
我们都有自己的一段悲情故事
We've all got our own sad stories, so...
管它呢
...screw it.
该玩的时候好好玩  不要有遗憾
Have fun, no regrets,
今朝有酒今朝醉
And live life like there's no tomorrow.
比如说
For instance,
我整晚都在想你
I have been thinking about you all night.
好吧
Well...
部分
Parts of you.
只是部分吗
Just parts?
比如说你的嘴唇
Like your lips.
很让人分神
They're very distracting.
真是个问题啊
It's a problem.
我忍不住想着要吻它们
And I can't stop thinking about kissing them.
那么
That so?
So...
还啰嗦什么呢
...what the hell, huh?
萨姆  你他妈去哪了
Sam, where the hell have you been?
跟卡拉在一起
With cara.
现在叫卡拉了
Oh, it's "cara" now.
你也不接个电话
And you're not picking up your phone.
我们正努力找那些血样呢
We were trying to find the blood samples.
-被人偷了  -是啊 我打赌也是
- Someone stole them.  - yeah, I'll bet.
什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
尼克在犯罪现场找到了花瓣
Nick found flower petals at the crime scenes.
是风信子
Hyacinths.
-那又怎样  -风信子
- So?   - hyacinths?
来自地中海的一个小岛
Mediterranean, from the -- from the island
那里正是海妖神话传说
Where the whole freakin' siren myth
开始流传的地方
started in the first place
好吧
Okay.
萨姆  卡拉有风信子
Sam, cara had hyacinth flowers.
你觉得卡拉是那个海妖吗
You think cara's the siren?
好吧  我查了一下她
Well, I did a little checking up on her.
她才在这个镇子待了两个月
She's only been in town for two months.
是吗  然后呢
Yeah, and?
她有个前夫
And she has an ex-husband.
一个死掉的前夫  卡尔·罗伯茨
A dead ex-husband -- carl roberts.
消失无影  无任何征兆
Dropped like a stone, no warning,
报道称其心脏病发
Supposedly a heart attack.
好吧  也许就是心脏病发
Well, maybe it was a heart attack.
你在开玩笑吧
You're kidding me.
我就是觉得不是她
Look, I just don't think it's her.
是什么让你如此坚定呢
And what makes you so sure?
我不知道  直觉吧
I don't know. a hunch.
直觉
A hunch?
我给你的是冰冷残酷的事实
I'm giving you cold, hard facts here,
你却回赠我一个直觉
And you're giving me a hunch?
你是不是跟她睡了
Did you sleep with her?
没
No.
胡扯  你跟她睡了
Holy crap. you did.
真像在演“本能”啊  你居然跟莎朗·斯通睡了
Middle of "basic instinct" and you bang sharon stone?
萨姆  现在你可能已经中了她的咒语了
Sam, you could be under her spell right now.
兄弟  我没中她的咒语
Dude, I'm not under her spell.
真不敢相信  伙计  我只是不明白
Unbelievable, man. I just don't get it.
什么
What?
没什么
Nothing.
不  你说
No. say it.
不 只是
No, it's just --
一开始是麦蒂逊  然后是露比  现在卡拉
First it's madison, and then ruby, and now cara.
你是怎么了  老是喜欢跟魔鬼上床
It's like what is with you and banging monsters?
迪恩  我告诉你  卡拉不是海妖
Look, dean, I'm telling you. it's not cara.
我觉得很好
I feel fine.
我打赌中咒语了
I'll bet you do.
你不信我
You don't trust me.
不  因为这可能是已经被海妖迷上的结果
No because this could be the siren talking.
就告诉我你在哪
Look, just tell me where you are.
我来见你  我们会把事情弄清楚的
I'll come meet you, and we'll figure things out.
不
No.
你认真的吗
Are you serious?
但愿我是在瞎说
I wish I weren't.
我来搞定这件事  萨姆  一个人
I got to handle this, sam, by myself.
萨姆有麻烦了  鲍比
sam's in trouble, bobby.
我恐怕海妖对他施了咒
I think the siren's worked her mojo on him.
收到留言立刻给我回电
Give me a call as soon as you get this.
怎么了  伙计
Hey, man. what's up?
我需要你帮忙
I need your help.
当然可以  要怎么做
Uh, sure. with what?
彻查  我们要找个人
Canvassing. we got to find somebody.
她刚刚才进去
She went in just a second ago.
干得漂亮
Nice work.
我们要跟进去吗
Should we follow her in?
不  不  不  我不想打草惊蛇
No, no, no. I don't want to tip her off.
等着看她和谁一起出来
I'm just waiting to see who she comes out with.
你觉得  怎么了
So you think, what...
她给这些人下药了
She's drugging these guys?
很有可能
Pretty much.
我知道你听了这话会有什么反应
I know how it sounds.
你确定
Are you sure about that?
这简直奇怪得要命
'cause it sounds like crazy on toast.
所有这些脱衣舞女
All these different strippers --
居然都是同一个姑娘
They're magically the same girl.
但之后她们又都不再是脱衣舞女了
But then they're not strippers at all --
成了奎因医生
It's dr. quinn?
这有点难以解释
It's kind of hard to explain,
但我有理由的  说得通的理由
But I have my reasons, and they're good ones.
所以你只要相信我就好
So you're just gonna have to trust me on it.
是啊
Yeah.
好
Okay.
我想可以
I guess.
谢谢
Thank you.
你这么说我很高兴
That's actually nice to hear.
那么假设她给被害者下了药
So, let's say she is drugging her vics.
她是怎么做到的
How's she pulling that off?
有可能用了注射器
She could be injecting them,
或者通过肢体接触来传播毒素
You know, or passing the toxin through physical contact.
也有可能是用她的唾液
Or it could be her saliva.
在你深吻它之前
You really should have wiped the lip of that thing
真该把它的嘴擦干净  迪恩
Before you drank from it, dean.
我才应该是你弟弟
I should be your little brother.
萨姆
Sam...
你不能相信他
...you can't trust him.
并表示可以相信我
Not like you can trust me.
事实上  我真的认为
In fact, I really feel
你应该把他赶走
Like you should get him out of the way
那样我们就能当兄弟了
So that we can be brothers...
永远
Forever.
是的
Yeah.
没错  你说的对
Yeah, you're right.
尼克  你在这儿干嘛
Nick, what are you doing here?
迪恩
Dean?
我必须告诉你  作为一个脱衣舞娘你真够丑的
I got to tell you, you're one butt-ugly stripper.
也许吧
Well, maybe.
但我得到了自己正想要的
But I got exactly what I wanted.
我得到了迪恩
I got dean.
迪恩  醒醒  老兄
Dean, come on, man.
那不是你  你能战胜它的
This isn't you. you can fight this.
放开我
Let me go.
为什么你不给他来一刀呢
Why don't you cut him
就在他的脖子上来一小下
Just a little on his neck right there?
迪恩完全属于我了
Dean's all mine.
你给他下了毒
You poisoned him.
不  我实现了他的愿望
No, I gave him what he needed.
那可不是什么穿丁字裤的婊子
And it wasn't some bitch in a g-string.
而是你
It was you.
一个敬仰他的弟弟
A little brother that looked up to him
一个他可以信任的弟弟
That he could trust.
现在他爱的是我
And now he loves me.
他会为我做任何事
He'd do anything for me.
告诉你  萨姆
And I got to tell you, sam,
这是一种热爱
That kind of devotion --
看着有人为你去杀人
Watching someone kill for you...
真是最至高无上的快感
...is the best feeling in the world.
就因为这个你把整个镇子都睡了
Is that why you're slutting all over town?
我厌倦了
I get bored.
我们都一样
Like we all do.
我想再度坠入爱河
And I want to fall in love again
一次又一次
And again and again.
告诉你  我对付过不少下流的混蛋
Tell you what, I have fought some nasty sons of bitches,
而你却是一个卑贱可悲的孬种
But you are one needy, pathetic loser.
你很快就不会这么想了
You won't feel that way in a minute.
不  不
No, no.
我知道你们两
So, I know you two
有许多不堪回首的记忆
Have a lot you want to get off your chests.
不如你们讨论一下
So why don't you discuss it...
最后活下来的那个就能永远和我在一起
And whoever survives can be with me forever?
我不知道是什么时候开始的
Well, I don't know when it happened.
也许是我在地狱的时候
Maybe when I was in hell.
也许是我凝视着你的时候
Maybe when I was staring right at you.
但是我所认识的萨姆已经不见了
But the sam I knew, he's gone.
那又怎样
That so?
跟恶魔之血和灵魂之类的鬼扯无关
And it's not the demon blood or the psychic crap.
而是一些小事
It's the little stuff --
那些谎言  那些秘密
The lies, the secrets.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
什么秘密
What secrets?
比如说  跟露比通电话
Phone calls to ruby, for one.
那我打电话还得经过你同意咯
So I need your say-so to make a phone call?
这正是关键
That's the point.
你有事瞒着我
You're hiding things from me.
你还有什么事没告诉我的
What else aren't you telling me?
跟你没关系
None of your business.
明白我刚的话了吧
See what I mean?
我们曾经在同一条战线上
We used to be in this together.
曾经互相依靠
We used to have each other's backs!
行  好吧
Okay, fine.
知道为什么不把露比的事告诉你
You want to know why I didn't tell you about ruby?
还有我们是怎样追捕莉莉丝的吗
And how we're hunting down lilith?
因为你要抓她还不够格  迪恩
Because you're too weak to go after her, dean.
你会拖我后腿
You're holding me back.
作为一个猎手我比你出色得多
I'm a better hunter than you are --
更强壮  更聪明
Stronger, smarter.
我能把你唯恐避之不及的恶魔控制住
I can take out demons you're too scared to go near.
一派胡言
That's crap.
你只会坐在那儿
You're too busy sitting around
自怨自艾
Feeling sorry for yourself,
唠叨那些你在地狱里折磨过的灵魂
Whining about all the souls you tortured in hell.
你别想再碍着我
You're not standing in my way anymore.
为了我  上吧  迪恩
Do it for me, dean.
有种再说遍我多窝囊  萨姆
Tell me again how weak I am, sam, huh?
我是怎么拖你后腿的
How I hold you back.
不
No.
No!
谢谢
Thanks.
苏打水
Soda?
你们是不是精力太旺盛啊
You boys are driving, ain't ya?
谢谢  鲍比
Thanks, bobby.
你  你来帮忙之前深藏不露
You know, you -- you hadn't shown up when you did --
你们又何尝不是呢
Done the same for me, more than once.
当然  你们只要拿起电话
Of course, you could have picked up a phone.
拨一通就能查到
Only took one call to figure out
那个尼克·门罗特工是假的
That agent nick monroe wasn't real.
你们两还好吧
You boys gonna be okay?
是的  没事
Yeah, fine.
是的  很好
Yeah, good.
那些海妖很险恶的
You know, those sirens are nasty things.
一旦它缠上你  总是感觉良好
That it got to you -- that's no reason to feel bad.
你要跟卡拉道别吗
You gonna say goodbye to cara?
不
Nah.
没兴趣
Not interested.
真的吗  为什么不呢
Really? why not?
有什么意义呢
What's the point?
看看你  相爱却又要别离
Well, look at you. love 'em and leave 'em.
迪恩  你知道我不是故意
Dean, look, you know I didn't mean
要说那些话的  对吗
The things I said back there, right?
只是中了海妖的咒语才这样的
That it was just the siren's spell talking?
当然  我也是
Of course. me too.
好吧
Okay.
那么  那么我们和好了
So -- so we're good?
对  和好了
Yeah, we're good.